Test driven development is when you write
测试驱动开发就是
tests before you write the code that's being tested.
在编写需要测试的代码之前先编写测试用例
This means your test would fail at first and you will know you
这意味着测试最初会失败
finished implementing a task when this test passes.
而在测试通过时 你就能了解到自己完成了任务
This way of developing code has a number of
这种开发代码的方式有很多优势
benefits that's made it a standard practice in software engineering.
使其成为了软件工程的标准实践
As a simple example,
举个简单的例子
let's say you have to write a function that checks
假设你要编写一个函数
whether a string is a valid email address.
检查字符串是否为有效的电子邮件地址
You think of a few factors to consider such as whether the string contains
你可以想到一些要考虑的因素 例如字符串是否包含
an "@" symbol and a period and write out a function that addresses them,
一个 @ 符号和一个句点 然后写出检测这些内容的函数
and then test it manually in your terminal.
在终端中手动测试
You input one valid and one invalid email address
输入一个有效和一个无效的电子邮件地址
to make sure it works properly, and it does.
来确保它可以正常工作 确实可以
You try a few more valid and invalid email addresses
你又尝试了更多有效和无效的电子邮件地址
and one of them gives back the wrong result.
其中一个给出了错误的结果
You realize you forgot to consider an edge case in your function,
你意识到自己忘记在函数中考虑边缘情况
so you go back and add that in.
所以返回去加入这种情况
Then, you test your function with another edge case you forgot to
然后你使用另一个忘记考虑的边缘情况测试功能
consider and edit your function again to fix this.
然后再次编辑函数来解决问题
Instead of doing all of this back and forth,
其实你可以不用来回做这些工作
you can try to create a test that checks for all the different scenarios and
而是尝试创建一个检查所有不同场景和边缘情况的测试
edge case as you can think of before even starting to write your function.
甚至在编写函数之前就开始考虑这些内容
This way, when you do start implementing your function,
这样 当你开始实现函数时
you can run this test to get immediate feedback on whether it works or
可以运行此测试 来获得有关函数是否有效的即刻反馈
not in all the ways you can think of as you tweak your function.
针对所有你可以想到的调整函数的方式
If your test passes,
如果测试通过
you know your implementation is done.
你就知道自己已经完成实现
In the future, when you refactor
将来 当你重构该函数
this function or make changes to other parts of your program,
或修改程序的其他部分
you can keep running this test to ensure your function still behaves as expected.
你可以继续运行此测试 来确保函数仍然按预期运行
This also helps ensure that your function behavior
这也有助于确保你的函数行为
is repeatable regardless of external parameters,
是可重复的 无论外部参数如何
such as hardware and time.
比如硬件和时间
When you first start writing tests,
当你第一次开始编写测试时
you will be slow and you will be tempted to
会很慢 你会更想
write implementation code before you write tests.
在编写测试之前先编写实现代码
Stick with it though and through practice,
坚持练习 通过实践
you will get faster.
你会变得更快
Eventually, you'll be able to write all kinds of tests in very little time.
最终你将能够在很短的时间内编写各种测试